[
  {
    "key": "1",
    "name": "Three-way mirror",
    "description": "Every triangle you collect counts as three.",
    "question": "How many Platonic solids are there?",
    "answer": 5
  }, {
    "key": "2",
    "name": "Four walls",
    "description": "Get four additional squares.",
    "question": "How many vertices does the icosahedron have?",
    "answer": 12
  }, {
    "key": "3",
    "name": "Pentagram",
    "description": "Get five additional pentagons.",
    "question": "Which Platonic solid consists of pentagons?",
    "answer": "dodecahedron"
  }, {
    "key": "4",
    "name": "Six times six",
    "description": "Get 6 additional hexagons.",
    "question": "How many Platonic solids consist of triangles?",
    "answer": 3
  }, {
    "key": "5",
    "name": "Three, four, five (Part 1)",
    "description": "Get 3 additional squares and pentagons.",
    "question": "How many Archimedean solids are there?",
    "answer": 13
  }, {
    "key": "6",
    "name": "Three, four, five (Part 2)",
    "description": "Get 5 additional triangles and squares.",
    "question": "According to Plato, which polyhedron was the building block of fire?",
    "answer": "tetrahedron"
  }, {
    "key": "7",
    "name": "Octagonal",
    "description": "Get 3 additional octagons.",
    "question": "What is the volume of a cube with side length 2?",
    "answer": 8
  }, {
    "key": "8",
    "name": "Pieces of eight",
    "description": "Get 4 additional triangles and hexagons.",
    "question": "How many faces does the Snub Dodecahedron have?",
    "answer": 92
  }, {
    "key": "9",
    "name": "Four, five, six",
    "description": "Get 5 additional squares and hexagons.",
    "question": "What Archimedean Solid has the shape of a soccer ball?",
    "answer": "truncated icosahedron"
  }, {
    "key": "10",
    "name": "100 corners!",
    "description": "Get 10 additional 10-gons.",
    "question": "Which molecule has the shape of a Truncated Icosahedron?",
    "answer": "c60"
  }, {
    "key": "11",
    "name": "Ten more squares",
    "description": "Get 10 additional squares.",
    "question": "Which polyhedron is the dual of the cube?",
    "answer": "octahedron"
  }, {
    "key": "12",
    "name": "Triangulate",
    "description": "Get 9 additional triangles.",
    "question": "What is the value of “Faces + Vertices – Edges” for every polyhedron?",
    "answer": 2
  }
]
